Guide to the Western Sudan Agricultural Research Project Records 1976-1986
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 1: On-Campus Correspondence Files
  - Related Projects/Reports--AID/CID
    - Project Documents, Work Copies, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 550)
    - Project Paper Factsheet and Amendment, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 551)
    - Project Reports, CID, 1979-1982 (Box 14, Folder 552)
    - Sudan Western Agriculture Research Project Paper, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 553)
  - Reports--Agriculture Research Corporation:
    - Agricultural Research Programs, February 1981 (Box 14, Folder 554)
    - "Cereal Crops In The Sudan," and "Soybean Production In The Sudan," 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 554.01)
    - South Darfur Research Program, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 555)
    - Kenneth L. Turk, "Organization and Administration of Agricultural Research in the Sudan," n.d. (Box 14, Folder 556)
  - Reports--External Evaluations: General, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 557-558)
  - Reports, Gum Arabic, Agricultural Research Corporation, 1979-1981 (Box 14, Folder 559)
  - Reports: Quarterly, 1979-1985 (Box 14, Folder 560-567)
  - Reports--Quarterly
    - Shawgi Amin, Project Engineer, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 568)
    - Trent Bunderson, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 569)
    - Richard Cook, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 570)
    - David Higgins, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 571)
    - Shirley Higgins, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 572)
    - Joe R. Gingrich, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 573)
    - Neil Patrick, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 574)
    - Joel M. Teitelbaum, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 575)
  - Reports--Status: General, 181 (Box 14, Folder 576)
  - Reports--Western Sudan Agricultural Research Project: Evaluation Team, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 577)
  - Reports--Western Sudan Agricultural Research Project: Internal Evaluation; Audits, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 578)
  - Reports--Winrock International, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 578.01)
  - Reports--World Bank
    - General, 1978-1986 (Box 14, Folder 579)
    - Staff Appraisal Report, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 580)
    - Sudan Agricultural Sector Survey, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 581)
  - Research: Guidelines for WSARP, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 581.01)
  - Research--Proposals and Projects
    - Agricultural Economics Research, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 582)
    - Agronomy (Seeds), 1982-1984 (Box 14, Folder 583)
    - Decertification, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 583.01)
    - Pest Management Research Program, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 584)
    - Range/Livestock Research, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 585-586)
    - Research Plans, 1984-1986 (Box 14, Folder 587-589)
    - Remote Sensing Proposal, Colorado State University, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 590)
    - Social Science/Anthropology Research, 1981-1984 (Box 14, Folder 591)
    - WSARP Work Plans (Drafts), 1982 (Box 14, Folder 592)
    - WSARP Work Plans, General Research Program and Plans, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 593)
    - WSARP Work Plans, Kadugli Research Center, Vol. III, Part A, 1982-1985 (Box 14, Folder 594)
  - Shipping--Mail
    - Airborne, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 595)
    - Air Express International, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 596)
    - Air Freight, 1982-1985 (Box 14, Folder 597)
    - Arkel, 1979-1986 (Box 14, Folder 598)
    - Circle Air Freight, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 599)
    - Federal Express, Mail APO, 1979-1983 (Box 15, Folder 600)
    - Freight Procedures, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 601)
    - Trade Wind Express, Mail Courier, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 602)
  - Supplies: Snake Anti-venom, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 603)
  - Travel
    - Frank P. Araujo, 1979-1981 (Box 15, Folder 604)
    - Lalit Arya, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 605)
    - Bill Bolander, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 606)
    - Trent Bunderson, 1983-1985 (Box 15, Folder 607)
    - C. Brent Cluff, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 608)
    - Richard Cook, 1982-1986 (Box 15, Folder 609)
    - Don Dwyer, 1980-1984 (Box 15, Folder 610)
    - Rita Fisher, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 611)
    - Tom and Nancy Gillard-Byers, 1984-1986 (Box 15, Folder 612)
    - Joe R. Gingrich, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 613)
    - Grube, Joachim-Grube, Zimmer, Inc., 1980-1985 (Box 15, Folder 614)
    - John and Jodi Deutsch Hannum, 1983-1985 (Box 15, Folder 615)
    - Robert Harwood, 1979-1981 (Box 15, Folder 616)
    - James Henson, 1979-1985 (Box 15, Folder 616.01-619)
    - David and Shirley Higgins, 1980-1985 (Box 15, Folder 620)
    - Anne Lemoyne and Chris Hogan, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 621)
    - Mack Johnson, 1979-1981 (Box 15, Folder 622)
    - Robert LaRocque, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 623)
    - Michael Mannion, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 624)
    - Lynn McDonald, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 625)
    - Barbara Michael, 1982-1985 (Box 15, Folder 626)
    - Jan C. Noel, 1980-1986 (Box 15, Folder 627-629)
    - Gerald Owens, 1981-1984 (Box 15, Folder 630)
    - Neil and Caryll Neil, 1982-1984 (Box 15, Folder 631)
    - James Riley, 1980-1985 (Box 15, Folder 632-635)
    - LeRoy Rogers, 1980-1984 (Box 15, Folder 636)
    - Miller Shurtleff, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 637)
    - Genevieve Smith-Thompson, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 638)
    - Mark Speece, 1985-1986 (Box 15, Folder 639)
    - Alice Spitzer, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 640)
    - Lee and Alice Stenquist, 1981-1983 (Box 15, Folder 641)
    - Bill Symons, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 642)
    - Joel and Maya Teitelbaum and Children, 1981-1984 (Box 15, Folder 643)
    - Tom Trail, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 644)
    - Phil Wandschneider, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 645)
    - T. Woldetatois, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 646)
  - Travel--Correspondence: General, 1980-1982 (Box 16, Folder 647)
  - Travel--Education Allowances
    - Lolit Arya, 1983-1985 (Box 16, Folder 648)
    - General, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 649)
    - Robert Harwood, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 650)
    - James Riley, 1980-1983 (Box 16, Folder 651-652)
    - Lee Stenquist, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 653)
    - Joel Teitelbaum, 1982-1984 (Box 16, Folder 653.01)
  - Travel--Household Moves and Consumables
    - Frank Araujo, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 654)
    - Lalit Arya, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 655)
    - H. Bergman, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 656)
    - W. Bunderson, 1980-1985 (Box 16, Folder 656.01)
    - Richard Cook, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 657)
    - General, 1981-1983 (Box 16, Folder 658)
    - Tom Gilard-Byers, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 659)
    - Joe Gingrich, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 660)
    - Joe Hannum, 1983-1986 (Box 16, Folder 661)
    - Robert Harwood, 1979-1982 (Box 16, Folder 662)
    - David Higgins, 1980-1983 (Box 16, Folder 663)
    - LeMayne Hogan, 1984-1986 (Box 16, Folder 664)
    - Barbara Michael, 1982-1984 (Box 16, Folder 665)
    - Gary Owens, 1982-1984 (Box 16, Folder 666)
    - Neil Patrick, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 667)
    - James Riley, 1980-1985 (Box 16, Folder 668)
    - Miller Shurtleff, 1979-1981 (Box 16, Folder 669)
    - Lee Stenquist, 1981-1983 (Box 16, Folder 670)
    - Joel Teitelbaum, 1981-1984 (Box 16, Folder 671)
    - Tsegazeab Woldetatois, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 672)
  - Travel--Intervievs: Roy H. Behnke, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 673)
  - Travel--Interviews: Walter G. Firestone, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 674)
  - Travel--Records, In-country: Travel Information, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 675)
  - Travel--Sudanese Personnel
    - Mohammad Saeed Bakheit, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 676)
    - Hamiel Burhon, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 677)
    - Dr. D. A. Dafalla, 1981-1985 (Box 16, Folder 678-679)
    - Babo Fadlalla, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 680)
    - Osman Khalifa, 1980-1982 (Box 16, Folder 681)
  - Travel--Sudanese Trainees
    - Abdelgadir A. Ageeb, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 682)
    - Sid Ahmed Beteik, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 683)
    - Farouk El-Hadi, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 684)
    - Mahmoud Mekki, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 685)
    - El-Tighani El Amin, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 686)
    - Hassan El-Awadi, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 687)
    - Mekk A. Omer, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 688)
    - Zakaria Sued, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 689)
  - U.S. AID: Mailbag Lists, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 690-691)
  - Vehicles: Fuel Needs, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 692)
  - Vehicles: INTSORMIL Vehicle Purchase, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 693)
  - Vehicles: Maintenance and Manuals, 1981-1983 (Box 16, Folder 694)
  - Vehicles: Miscellaneous, 1979-1983 (Box 16, Folder 695)
  - Workshops
    - Arid Lands Conference, "Call for Papers," 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 696)
    - Campus-wide Seminar, 8th Africa Symposium, 1982-1985 (Box 16, Folder 697)
    - Centro Internacional De Mejoramiento De Maiz Y Trigo (CIMMYT), On Farm Research, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 698)
    - Farming Systems, 1983-1985 (Box 16, Folder 699-700)
    - Farming Systems Workshop, Tucson, Arizona, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 701)
    - Planning Workshop for Ghogola Gawazat, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 702)
    - Regional Workshops, ARC/WSARP, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 703)
    - Research Planning Meeting, El Fasher, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 704)
    - Strego Workshops, L.J. Musselman, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 705)
- Series 2: Records from the Sudan Office
  - Administrative Meetings: In-Country, 1982-1984 (Box 16, Folder 706)
  - Administrative Notes: Shirley Higgins, 1980-1986 (Box 16, Folder 707)
  - Airplane Schedules, 1980-1985 (Box 17, Folder 708)
  - Airplane-UNICEF: Requests, Bills, 1982-1985 (Box 17, Folder 709)
  - Audit: Recommendations and Requests, 1982-1984 (Box 17, Folder 710)
  - Budget
    - Budget Development, 1980-1983 (Box 17, Folder 711-714)
    - CID Trust Fund Budget, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 715)
    - Cost Estimates, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 716)
    - Long-Term Budget, Working Papers, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 717)
  - Building Maintenance: Work Orders, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 718)
  - Contract and Amendments: CID-AID, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 719)
  - Correspondence
    - Correspondence, General, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 720)
    - CID, 1981-1984 (Box 17, Folder 721)
    - D. A. Dafalla, 1981-1985 (Box 17, Folder 722)
    - Finance, 1983-1985 (Box 17, Folder 723)
    - Noel-Henson, 1981-1985 (Box 17, Folder 724)
    - International Medical Systems; LeMoyne Hogan, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 725)
    - Robert LaRocque, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 726)
    - Memorandum, AID/Embassy, 1981-1985 (Box 17, Folder 727)
    - Sudanese Employees, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 728)
    - Joel Teitelbaum, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 729)
    - Telephone Calls to WSU, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 730)
    - U.S. AID--Embassy, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 730.01)
  - Correspondence Log Sheets
    - General, Numbers 100 through 125, 1980-1985 (Box 17, Folder 731)
    - Log 100, WSU Correspondence, 1980-1985 (Box 17, Folder 732)
    - Log 101, Personnel, Receipts, 1981-1984 (Box 17, Folder 733)
    - Log 102, Procurement, Personnel, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 734)
    - Log 103, Financial, 1980-1983 (Box 17, Folder 735)
    - Log 104, INTSORMIL, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 736)
    - Log 105, Financial Reports, Project and Trip Reports, 1980-1986 (Box 17, Folder 737)
    - Log 106, Karplen, 1980-1985 (Box 17, Folder 738)
    - Log 107, Trust Fund, Progress Report, 1980-1984 (Box 17, Folder 739)
    - Log 108, Procurements, Waivers and Correspondence, 1980-1985 (Box 17, Folder 740-741)
    - Log 109, Dafalla, Hogan, Higgins, Noel, Hannum, WSARD, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 742)
    - Log 110, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 743)
    - Log 111, Shipping Documents, Purchases; Patrick, Owen, 1982-1984 (Box 18, Folder 744)
    - Log 112, Riley; Packing List, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 745)
    - Log 113, Higgins; Packing List, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 746)
    - Log 114, Hannum; Packing List, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 747)
    - Log 115, Gillard-Byers; Packing List, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 748)
    - Log 116, Bunderson; Packing List, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 749)
    - Log 117, Publications/WSARP Post, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 750)
    - Log 118, Cook; Packing List, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 751)
    - Log 119, Travel, Procurement and Shipping, 1983-1985 (Box 18, Folder 752)
    - Log 120, Trip Reports, Travel Notes, Research Committee Minutes, 1981-1983 (Box 18, Folder 753)
    - Log 121, Attendance Records, Resume, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 754)
    - Log 122-124, Finance, 1982-1985 (Box 18, Folder 755-757)
    - Log 125, Meeting Notes, 1981-1983 (Box 18, Folder 758)
    - Log 126, Senior Staff Reports, 1983-194 (Box 18, Folder 759-760)
    - Log 127, Reports, 1981-1986 (Box 18, Folder 761-762)
    - Log 128, Monthly and Trip Reports, 1980-1983 (Box 18, Folder 763)
    - Log 129, General, Shoppeir Guide to Khartom, 1983-1985 (Box 18, Folder 764)
    - Log 130, Project Implementation Order, Participant, 1983-1985 (Box 18, Folder 765)
    - Log 131, Quarterly Reports, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 766)
    - Log 132, Oceanair International, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 767)
    - Log 133, Leases, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 768)
    - Log 134, Maintenance, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 769)
    - Log 135, Personnel Files, 1982-1985 (Box 18, Folder 770-771)
    - Log 136, Personnel File, Riley, 1980-1984 (Box 18, Folder 772)
  - Expenditures, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 773)
  - Expenditures
    - Account Reconciliation, Report, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 774)
    - Accounting Reports, Citibank Reconciliations, 1980-1983 (Box 19, Folder 775)
    - Administrative Assistant, Monthly Report, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 776)
    - CID Revolving Trust Fund, 1981-1984 (Box 19, Folder 777)
    - CID Trust Account, Direct AID Expenditures, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 778)
    - CID-WSARP Trust Account, May 1982-July 1984 (Box 19, Folder 779-803)
    - CID-WSARP Trust Account, August 1984-December 1985 (Box 20, Folder 804-818)
    - CID-WSARP Trust Account, General, 1979-1986 (Box 20, Folder 819)
    - Educational, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 820)
    - Gasoline, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 821)
    - KARPLEN Account, 1980-1982 (Box 20, Folder 822)
    - Receipts, Monthly, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 823)
    - Reconciliation of Cash Advance, 1980-1983 (Box 20, Folder 824)
    - Sudan Dollar Account, January 1981-March 1981 (Box 20, Folder 825-827)
    - Sudan Dollar Account, April 1981-March 1985 (Box 21, Folder 828-860)
    - Sudan Dollar Account, April 1985-December 1985 (Box 22, Folder 861-864)
    - Trust Fund Account, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 865)
    - Trust Fund Account, CID, Temporary, January 1981- June 1982 (Box 22, Folder 866-872)
    - WSU Revolving Fund, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 873)
    - World Bank, Consolidated Statement, 1979-1981 (Box 22, Folder 874)
    - World Bank, Working Papers, 1979-1981 (Box 22, Folder 875)
  - Financial Reports, 1979-1984 (Box 22, Folder 876)
  - Financial Statements, 1981-1983 (Box 22, Folder 877)
  - Inventory, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 878)
  - Library, El Obered, WSARP Publication List, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 879)
  - Personnel: Leave Days, Official, 1981-1985 (Box 22, Folder 880)
  - Personnel: Medivac, W. T. Bunderson, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 881)
  - Project Notebook: Loose Papers, 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 882)
  - Project Notebook: Jan Noel, 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 883)
  - Project Notebook: Gary Owens, 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 884)
  - Purchasing: Procedures, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 884.01)
  - Report: Evaluation Team Mid-term Report, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 885)
  - Travel: Expatriate Staff, 1979-1984 (Box 22, Folder 886)
  - Travel: In-country, Requests, 1980-1985 (Box 22, Folder 887-888)
  - WSARP
    - Advisory Committee, WSU, 1979-1984 (Box 23, Folder 889)
    - AID Leased Properties, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 890)
    - AID--Project Documents, Copies, Project Paper Amendment, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 891-892)
    - AID Reports--Agricultural Sector Support Report, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 893)
    - AID Reports on Sudan, 1982-1985 (Box 23, Folder 894)
    - Agricultural Engineering/Technology, Energy, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 895)
    - Agricultural Research Project, Preparation Report (Draft), 1977 (Box 23, Folder 896)
    - Agricultural Research Project, Staff Appraisal Report, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 897-898)
    - Agricultural Sector Survey, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 898.01)
    - Agronomy/Horticulture, Drought Resistance/ Water Stress of Plan, 1973-1984 (Box 23, Folder 899-900)
    - Agronomy/Horticulture, Peat Management/Crop Protection, 1979-1983 (Box 23, Folder 901-902)
    - "An Assessment of Title XII Strengthening Program," by David Hanseb and Paul Van Buren, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 903)
    - Anthropology/Social Science/Nomadism, Computer Searches, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 904)
    - Computer Searches/Bibliographies, Livestock/ Range Management/Veterinary Medicine, 1979-1984 (Box 23, Folder 905)
    - Concepts Paper, Country Development Strategy Statement, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 906)
    - CID Project Documents, Project Announcement, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 906.01)
    - CID Project Documents, Proposal Paper, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 906.02)
    - Construction Supervision Report, 1981-1985 (Box 23, Folder 906.03)
    - Contract, Budget, 1979-1982 (Box 23, Folder 907)
    - Contract, Correspondence, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 908)
    - Contract, Correspondence, CID, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 909)
    - Contracts, AID, Project Agreement, 1978-1981 (Box 23, Folder 910)
    - Contracts, CID, Contract/Amendments, 1979-1986 (Box 23, Folder 910.01)
    - Contracts, IADS, Credit Agreement, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 910.02)
    - Contracts, Miscellaneous Contracts/Leases, Residences Leases, 1979-1986 (Box 23, Folder 911)
    - Contracts, Miscellaneous Contracts (Box 23, Folder 911.01)
    - Contracts, Project Implementation Orders/Technical Services, 1979-1987 (Box 23, Folder 912)
    - Contracts, Present/Proposed Contract Wording, AIDS, CID, 1979-1985 (Box 23, Folder 913)
    - Contracts, World Bank, Credit Agreement, 1974-1986 (Box 23, Folder 914)
    - Evaluation, Design Team, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 915)
    - Extension, Applications, Reports, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 916)
    - Extension, Position Terminations and Related Correspondence, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 917)
    - Field Staff (WSU), Advisor, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 918)
    - Field Staff (WSU), Advisor, Correspondence (Riley), 1980-1985 (Box 24, Folder 919-923)
    - Field Staff (WSU), Agricultural Engineer, 1980-1983 (Box 24, Folder 924)
    - Field Staff (WSU), Agronomist, 1981-1983 (Box 24, Folder 925)
    - Field Staff (WSU), Chief of Party, 1981-1984 (Box 24, Folder 926)
    - Field Staff (WSU), Equipment, Utilities Maintenance, Operations, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 927)
    - Field Staff (WSU), General, 1979-1984 (Box 24, Folder 928)
    - Field Staff (WSU), Livestock, Production Specialist, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 929)
    - Field Staff (WSU), Salary Information, 1981-1984 (Box 24, Folder 930)
    - Field Staff (WSU), Social Scientist, Applications, 1979-1981 (Box 24, Folder 931-933)
    - Field Staff (WSU), "Sudan, Facts and Figures,-, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 934)
    - "Groundnut Innoculation in Sudan," by T. E. Loynachan, MA, Hadad-Iowa State, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 935)
    - Guide to Reference Materials. 1982 (Box 24, Folder 936)
    - Implementation, Background Planning, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 937)
    - Implementation, Early Planning, 1978-1980 (Box 24, Folder 938)
    - Implementation--Work Plans, Planning, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 939)
    - Implementation--Work Plans, Planning Meeting Report, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 940)
    - Implementation--Work Plans, Planning Meeting Correspondence, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 941)
    - Implementation--Work Plans, Scope of Work, Background, Work Copies, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 942)
    - Implementation--Work Plans, Scope of Work, Correspondence, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 943)
    - Implementation--Work Plans, Scope of Work, Report, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 944)
    - International Agricultural Development Service, Project Documents, Sudan Research Capabilities, 1977-1979 (Box 24, Folder 944.01)
    - Maintenance, Machine Vehicles, 1974-1979 (Box 24, Folder 945)
    - Net Export Value of Sudanese Exports, WSARP Related Reports, 1979-1983 (Box 24, Folder 946)
    - Quarterly Reports (Riley), 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 947)
    - Reference Materials, 1969-1985 (Box 24, Folder 947.01-947.02)
    - Reports, African Pastoral/Livestock Development Issues Paper, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 948)
    - Reports, "A Proposal to Assist the Goverment of Sudan in Implementing the Blue Nile Integrated Agricultural Development Project," by Development Alternatives, Inc., 1979 (Box 25, Folder 949)
    - Reports, Rural Planning Unit, South Kordofan, Interim Report, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 950)
    - Staff Notes (includes Lesotho #953, 1986), 1984-1987 (Box 25, Folder 951-953)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Agricultural Economics, Applicants, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 954)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Agricultural Economics Research Associate, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 955)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Agricultural Economist, Selection Process, 1980-1982 (Box 25, Folder 956)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Agronomy Candidates, 1982-1984 (Box 25, Folder 957-958)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Airplane Pilot Position, Implementation/Work Plans, 1979-1981 (Box 25, Folder 959)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Animal Production, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 960)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Background Materials, Policies, Procedures; Implementation/Work Plans, 1980-1985 (Box 25, Folder 961)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Chief Administrative Officer, 1979-1983 (Box 25, Folder 962)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Chief of Party, Selection Process, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 963)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Chief of Party, Top Candidates, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 964)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Chief of Party Candidates, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 965)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Classified Staff Support Positions, Implementation/Work Plans, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 966)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Land/Water Specialist, Selection Process, 1981-1983 (Box 25, Folder 967)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Land/Water Specialist, Other Applicants, 1981-1983 (Box 25, Folder 968)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Land/Water Specialist, Top Candidates, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 969)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Libraries, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 970)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Maintenance and Operations Advisor, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 971)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Miscellaneous Positions, 1981-1984 (Box 25, Folder 972)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Personnel, W. Trent Bunderson, 1980-1985 (Box 25, Folder 973-975)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Personnel, Dave Coahran, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 976)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Personnel, Richard H. Cook, 1981-1985 (Box 25, Folder 977)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Personnel, Richard, H. Cook, 1982-1984 (Box 26, Folder 978)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Personnel, Dr. Thomas Gillard-Byers, 1984-1986 (Box 26, Folder 979-980)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Personnel, Genevieve Smith-Thompson, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 981)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Personnel, Mark Speece, 1984-1986 (Box 26, Folder 982)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Personnel, Dr. Tsegazeab Woldetatois, 1984-1986 (Box 26, Folder 983-984)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Personnel, Milton (Tony) Wright, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 985)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Production Specialists, 1980-1985 (Box 26, Folder 986)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Range Management, 1980-1984 (Box 26, Folder 987)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Research Associate, (Agricultural Economics), 1982-1983 (Box 26, Folder 988)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Research Associate, (Social Science), 1980-1982 (Box 26, Folder 989)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Roles and Responsibilities, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 990)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Social Scientist, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 991)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Social Scientist Candidates, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 992)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Staff Projections, 1980-1984 (Box 26, Folder 993)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Statements to U.S. House of Representatives, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 994)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Stores/Inventory Specialist, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 995)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Sudanese Staffing, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 996)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Vehicle/Equipment Position, 1979-1984 (Box 26, Folder 997)
    - Staffing--Personnel, WSARP Staff, "Who is Who," 1978-1985 (Box 26, Folder 998-999)